Gary Reid

(253) 651.0309 | garyreidmusic@gmail.com

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Creative 12-year professional musician with experience and formal education in Graphic and Digital Design, currently taking Web Development classes including HTML, CSS, and JavaScript. Skilled in Adobe Creative Suite (Photoshop, Illustrator, etc.) Well immersed into many cultures by entertaining people around the world in over a dozen countries. Eleven years of experience in logistics, retail, and customer service with a positive friendly approach. I am seeking a position as a member of a team focused on positive growth.

EDUCATION & EXPERIENCE

<u>Digital Video and Web Design Certificate</u>, San Diego College of Continuing Education ('21-'23)

- Storyboard, Plan, and Execute Digital Media Projects, Start-To-Finish
- Edit Video Clips using Adobe Premiere Pro and AfterEffects.
- Create Vector-Based Graphics using Adobe Illustrator
- Design, Animate, and Optimize Images using Adobe Photoshop
- Create and edit Animated Banner Ads using Adobe AfterEffects

Software Proficiency

- Adobe Creative Suite
- Open Office / Microsoft Office
- GitHub
- HTML, CSS, JavaScript

- iMovie
- GIMP Image Manipulation
- Google / Microsoft Calendars
- Logic Pro (Digital Audio Workstations)

Additional Skills

- Team Worker
- Creatively Minded
- 38 Years in the Workforce
- Big-picture perspective

- Diligent and Focused
- Proficient using Mac OS & PC
- Solo World Traveler
- Adapts easily to New Situations

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

2011 - 2023	Self-Employed Musician, Guitarist, Singer - @GaryReidMusic everywhere
2005 - 2008	Office Worker, Temporary Positions - Manpower Inc., Boston, MA
1995 - 2004	Warehouse Manager, Shipping Receiving and Inventory Control – Triad Direct, Canton, MA
1988 - 1993	Retail Customer Service Positions – Various Companies, Boston, MA
1989 - 1991	Printshop Operator, Graphic Design and Printing Press – Norwell, MA